https://www.primaindustrie.com/privacy/

Information on the data processing
This section has the purpose of inform the people whom access the site www.primaindustrie.com about the fundamental aspects of the data processing.
Useful Contacts
Prima Industrie S.p.A. is the Company that process your personal data and by Law is considered Data Controller of the data processing. As it, it is accountable to guarantee the application of the organisational and technical measures necessary and adequate to protect Your personal data. The headquarter of the Company Via Antonelli 32—10093 Collegno (To) – Italy (Tel +39 011 41031).
Furthermore, the Company has nominated the Data Protection Officer in charge to guarantee the respect of the regulation to protect Your Privacy, that can be contacted for topic regarding the processing of Your data, at the following address (dpo@primaindustrie.com).
Further information on your rights may be found on the section “Your rights”.
Type of Data collected
Between your Personal Data collected by the Company, in autonomous way or through third parties, there are: anagrafical data, fiscal and economical data, telephonic, telefax and e-mail addresses, bank account details, data related to the structure and company organisation, data related to the adequate fulfillment of obligations, statistical data on sells, other company data necessary to the fulfillment of obligations related to present and future contracts and/or provided by the law, nontheless for statistical, commercial, marketing, promotional and credit safeguard purposes.
Are object of processing also informations related to the personal professional experience structured as curriculum vitae.
Purposes of processing
Personal data are collected, consulted and processed for the following purposes:
2.1 –Basic purposes
Fulfillment of obligations derived by deals of supply of goods and/or services between the parties both by contractual and pre-contractual means, in particular reference to their execution and the payment of the due fees. The fulfillment of the obligations derived by the communitarian regulation, and by laws and regulations in particular related to the accounting, fiscal, safety, order and public security topic. The fulfillment of the procedures adopted with the purpose of the certification ISO 9001:2000 between them to periodically measure the degree of customer satisfaction. Assert the rights also by third parties in judicial, arbitration, administrative venue.
2.2 – Selection of the personnel purposes
Carry out research, selection and evaluation of personnel.
The processing of Your data for the purposes specified before do not require your consent. You can get further information on your rights and how to exercise them in the section “Your rights”.
Furthermore the Company, only with your free, specific, informed and unambiguous consent, may use Your data to:
2.3 – Marketing purposes
Send communications for the need of monitoring the relation with the customers.
Plan and execute operational marketing activities.
Inform you about commercial and promotional activities, also for goods/services that are different from which defined in the supply relation.
In this case, where this purpose is foreseen, will be required your specific consent.
2.4 – Profilation purpose
Assign a probabilistic value of membership to give the data related to the composition of its audience for purposes related to the optimization of the contents and/or advertising.
Analyse the experience of navigation on the website to analyse your preferences and/or tastes.
In this case, where this purpose is foreseen, will be required your specific consent.
Related to this, we send you to what better specified in the Cookie section.
Communication and access to your personal data
The Company – without asking your consent – may communicate your personal data to a category of recipes better indicated later, as example: Companies of the Group, due to their respective professional skills to physical and/or legal persons, public and private subjects, tax offices, bodies order and public security, banking institutions, companies specialized in the management of payments, law firms and tax consultancy, public authorities or administrations for the fulfillment of the law, financing and transport companies.
The same data may be brought to the attention of the employees and/or collaborators by their respective duties and responsibilities, as well as consultants and collaborators as external managers, to whom we will request treatment in accordance with the provisions of the national provisions. and European laws on privacy.
Data Retention period for Your personal data
The Company will retain Your personal data until the conclusion of the contract and thereafter for the period of 10 years (term beyond which the rights arising from the contract will be prescribed) except for the data at the point 2.2, because for such processing, the Company will delete your data collected during the registration after 24 months since your last access to the system.
For more information on specific aspects regarding cancellation, contact the Company.
Your rights
With reference to the data processed, the Company guarantees the possibility of:
obtain confirmation of the existence or not of personal data concerning you and their copy in intelligible form;
obtain the updating, correction or integration of your data;
request the deletion of your data, within the terms permitted by law, or request that they are anonymised;
object, in whole or in part, for legitimate reasons, to the processing of personal data concerning you;
limit the processing, in case of violation, request for rectification or opposition;
request the portability of electronically processed data, provided on the basis of consent or contract;
withdraw consent to the processing of your data, if provided for.
With this purpose, the Company provides the contact of the Data Protection Officer (DPO), to which the interested party can submit his/her requests for free, by sending an email to the following contact: dpo@primaindustrie.com
We inform you that the Company undertakes to respond to your requests within one month, except in the case of particular complexity, so it may take up to 3 months. In any case, the Company will explain the reason for waiting within one month of your request. The outcome of your request will be provided in writing or in electronic format.
In case you request the correction, the cancellation and the limitation of the treatment, the Company undertakes to communicate the results of your requests to each of the recipients of your data, unless this proves impossible or involves a disproportionate effort.
It is recalled that the withdrawal of consent does not affect the lawfulness of the treatment based on consent before revocation.  The Company specifies that a possible contribution may be requested if its applications are manifestly unfounded, excessive or repetitive, in this regard the Company has a register to track its requests for intervention.
Cookie Policy
According to the art.13 of the legislative decree n. 196/2003, Code regarding the protection of personal data, of the EU Regulation 679/2016 and in compliance with the provisions of Regulation 229/2014 of the Guarantor for the Protection of Personal Data, this “Cookie Policy” is intended to provide information on types, purpose and methods of use / management of cookies required by this site.
Characteristics and purposes of the cookies
Cookies are small strings of text that a site sends to the user’s device in order to optimize navigation and services offered, to improve the functionality and use of the site. Cookies are used to manage authentication, monitor sessions and store user preferences.
Cookies can be saved on the device and remain active for a variable duration or cancel with the closing of the browser.
Some cookies are essential as they support essential functions of our website, such as storing the items included in the cart or access to restricted areas. In addition to browsing cookies, or session cookies, this site also uses the functionality cookies, which allow you to remember the choices made by the user (such as the language or country of origin) and to offer an advanced and personalized service.
We also use technical cookies to track, in accordance with current legislation, the acceptance of cookies.
Technical Cookies
Technical cookies are used on the Website only to make possible Your navigation on it and allow you of using its functionalities. Are always first party cookies, that are used by us on the Website.
Some technical cookies are essential to give you an optimal navigation experience o to allow you to authenticate on the website, as example to buy on the Website or log into Your reserved area (navigation cookie). Navigation cookies are normally session cookies and, though, once you close the browser, they get disactivated.
Other technical cookies are useful to allow you to store some of your preferences (for example, the language or country of origin) without having to reset them during subsequent visits (so-called function cookies). For this reason, functionality cookies are often persistent cookies, as they remain stored on your computer even after the browser is closed, until the expiration date provided for them or until you have decided to delete them.
As required by current legislation on privacy, for the installation of these cookies your prior consent is not required. Of course you are free to block the installation of technical cookies by changing the settings of your browser. Consider, however, that by blocking the installation of technical cookies, or subsequently eliminating them, the ability to access the Site, to use all or part of it, to enable or disable certain functions or receive certain services could be in whole or in part compromised.
Profilation Cookies
Profiling cookies are used to create your user profile, based on the preferences and tastes you have shown while browsing the Internet, and to send messages consistent with your profile. In this way the messages you could possibly receive may be more interesting for you.
As required by current legislation on privacy, for the installation of these cookies your prior consent is required. For this reason, when accessing particular sections of the site that install this type of cookie, a special banner is displayed, which informs you that (i) profiling cookies are used on this section of the Website and that (ii) is your consent is required for them to be installed. Should you express your consent to the installation of cookies in this way, we will keep track of your consent through a special technical cookie.
Naturally you are free to block the installation of profiling cookies at any time, without the possibility of visiting the site and enjoying its contents in any way compromised.
Our profiling cookies are installed by Salesforce Pardot.
These cookies are permanent and have a maximum duration of 10 years. Here is the list of cookies used by Prima Industrie S.p.A., with an indication of the ways in which it can oppose their installation:
Category: Necessary
COOKIE NAME
SUPPLIER
TYPE
EXPIRING
INSTRUCTIONS TO OPPOSITION
__cfduid
primapower.com
Mail to: dpo@primaindustrie.com
Furthermore, profiling cookies are installed by third parties, who act as autonomous data controllers (third party cookies) as better specified in the following:
Salesforce Pardot
Pardot is the Marketing Automation platform provided by Salesforce.com, inc. which tracks visitors and potential clients activities on the website and on the Landing Pages by setting cookies on their browsers.
The combined use of proprietary and third-party cookies is the standard in the marketing automation sector. Pardot cookies do not store personally identifiable information, but only a unique identifier.
For more information write an email to dpo@primaindustrie.com
Third parties cookie
During navigation, the user may receive on his device even “third-party” cookies, set by websites or web servers other than the one you are currently visiting. These services allow you to perform, for example, interactions with social networks, or other external platforms. It is possible that, even if the user does not use the service, it collects traffic data relating to the pages in which it is installed.
The installation of cookies and other tracking systems operated by third parties can not be technically controlled by the site operator, each specific reference is therefore to be considered indicative. For more information, please refer to information on any third-party services:
Google+ e YouTube
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
Google Analytics
The site uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses a set of cookies to collect information, generate usage statistics, monitor and improve site performance (performance cookies). All information collected through these cookies are aggregated and anonymous, without personal identification of individual visitors.
For more information, or disable this feature, please refer to the following links:
https://www.google.it/policies/privacy/partners/
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
Cookie management
By default almost all the browser are set to automatically accept the cookies. The user can decide to to disable the use of cookies or limit their functions by customizing the settings of your browser. Through the browser preferences it is also possible to delete the cookies installed in the past. It is important to note that disabling, blocking or deleting cookies may adversely affect the user experience and functionality of our website. Even the deactivation of third-party cookies could interfere with the proper functioning of the site.
Instructions on how to manage cookies in different browsers are available at the following links:
Chrome
Firefox
Internet Explorer
Safari
Opera
Continuing browsing by closing the information banner or clicking in any part of the page or scrolling to highlight further content, implies acceptance and understanding of this Cookie Policy and cookies will be set and used normally. The user will always have the possibility to remove these cookies at any time through the methods described above.
